Guide to the Time Inc. Sports Illustrated Editorial Records 1969-1988 MS 3009-RG 34
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Senior Editor Patricia Ryan Files, 1970-1974; 9 Linear feet in 10 record cartons
  - Correspondence: Gammon, Clive, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Gerber, Dan, Jr., 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Gilbert, Bil, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Gilbert, Sam / Bill Walton, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Harrison, Jim, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Haveman, Ernest, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Hjortsberg, William, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Hoagland, Edward, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Holland, Gerry, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Johnston, Richard, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Jordan, Pat, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Kane, Marty, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: McGuane, Thomas, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: McIlvanney, Hugh, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: Merrill, Sam, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: Mitchell, Carleton, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: Mano, D. Keith, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: Moore, Kenny, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: Plimpton, George, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: Rau, Ron: Arctic Shrew, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: Reed, J. D., 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: Revson, Peter J. R. / Leon Mandel: Speed with Style, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: Robertson, Bob, 1973 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: Schulian, John, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: Sharnick, M.: Arthur Mercante, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: Smith, Mason (Tim), 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence: Telander, Rick, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence: Tippette, Giles, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence: Whall, Hugh, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence: Whittaker, James D., 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence: Wright, Steve: Excerpt: I'd Rather Be Wright, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence: Yardley, Jonathan, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence: Yates, Brock, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 42)
  - Memoranda to Roy Terrell, 1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 43)
  - Text Department, 1971-1974 (Offsite-box 4111, Folder 44-47)
- Series IV. Associate Editor Joseph Carroll Correspondence, 1970; 0.33 Linear feet in 25 folders
  Records from Joseph Carroll contain correspondence to place articles or excerpts from outside writers. Outside writers include those from other magazines (sometimes other Time Inc. magazines), freelancers, and some amateurs. Files do not always have correspondence from the writer and may only contain internal correspondence regarding their article or excerpt. Topics include story ideas, submissions, the logistics of publishing accepted articles, and payment amounts. The correspondence is similar to that in Ray Cave's and Patricia Ryan's files.
  Folders I and U are empty.
  This series remains in the original alphabetical order.
  - Correspondence: A-Z, 1970 (Offsite-box 4102, Folder 29-53)